{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205885880","data":{"timestamp":" 947205885879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_t-a-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205890005","data":{"timestamp":" 947205890005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_y-p-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205896198","data":{"timestamp":" 947205896198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_i-l-v"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205900343","data":{"timestamp":" 947205900343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-t-h"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205905058","data":{"timestamp":" 947205905058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_h-l-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205909627","data":{"timestamp":" 947205909627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_h-l-b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205914471","data":{"timestamp":" 947205914471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_y-l-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205923172","data":{"timestamp":" 947205923172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_z-l-j"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205927265","data":{"timestamp":" 947205927265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_e-l-k"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205931130","data":{"timestamp":" 947205931130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_p-l-z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947205936908","data":{"timestamp":" 947205936907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 64b89bdd-8f10-4292-8be1-31fdd6554d86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.show.100"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_l_p-l-z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206008176","data":{"timestamp":" 947206008176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_k-w-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206105819","data":{"timestamp":" 947206105818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-r-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206109992","data":{"timestamp":" 947206109992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_o-ch-l"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206113205","data":{"timestamp":" 947206113205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-u-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206118409","data":{"timestamp":" 947206118409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-m-v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206126714","data":{"timestamp":" 947206126714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_u-i-l"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206136922","data":{"timestamp":" 947206136922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206140669","data":{"timestamp":" 947206140668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_z-l-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206192630","data":{"timestamp":" 947206192629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_v-ch-l"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206203935","data":{"timestamp":" 947206203935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_y-e-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206209714","data":{"timestamp":" 947206209712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 876b9ade-40cd-465d-8dc9-a9bcdba00908"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_l_y-e-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206241147","data":{"timestamp":" 947206241145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_w_l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206247817","data":{"timestamp":" 947206247817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_o_ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206254470","data":{"timestamp":" 947206254470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206261156","data":{"timestamp":" 947206261156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_l_p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206267810","data":{"timestamp":" 947206267810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_h_r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206274466","data":{"timestamp":" 947206274465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206281125","data":{"timestamp":" 947206281125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_l_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206287787","data":{"timestamp":" 947206287787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_l_i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206294418","data":{"timestamp":" 947206294418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_l_f"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206301056","data":{"timestamp":" 947206301055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_l_b"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206313163","data":{"timestamp":" 947206313163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" d1d93055-de18-4815-b94e-28663b305eaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_k_l_b"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206328665","data":{"timestamp":" 947206328664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206332192","data":{"timestamp":" 947206332191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206333804","data":{"timestamp":" 947206333803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206340550","data":{"timestamp":" 947206340550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206342143","data":{"timestamp":" 947206342142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206344422","data":{"timestamp":" 947206344421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206346059","data":{"timestamp":" 947206346059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206348639","data":{"timestamp":" 947206348637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206350234","data":{"timestamp":" 947206350233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206352417","data":{"timestamp":" 947206352417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206354031","data":{"timestamp":" 947206354030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206356514","data":{"timestamp":" 947206356513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206358109","data":{"timestamp":" 947206358108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206360317","data":{"timestamp":" 947206360317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206361911","data":{"timestamp":" 947206361910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206379748","data":{"timestamp":" 947206379748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206381344","data":{"timestamp":" 947206381344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206385173","data":{"timestamp":" 947206385173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206386786","data":{"timestamp":" 947206386785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206392443","data":{"timestamp":" 947206392443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206394053","data":{"timestamp":" 947206394053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206396639","data":{"timestamp":" 947206396639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206398251","data":{"timestamp":" 947206398251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206400727","data":{"timestamp":" 947206400727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206402357","data":{"timestamp":" 947206402356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206404535","data":{"timestamp":" 947206404534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206406138","data":{"timestamp":" 947206406137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206408414","data":{"timestamp":" 947206408413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206410009","data":{"timestamp":" 947206410008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206412094","data":{"timestamp":" 947206412093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206413684","data":{"timestamp":" 947206413684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206416602","data":{"timestamp":" 947206416601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206418222","data":{"timestamp":" 947206418221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206420586","data":{"timestamp":" 947206420586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206422177","data":{"timestamp":" 947206422176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206424374","data":{"timestamp":" 947206424373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206425972","data":{"timestamp":" 947206425971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206428834","data":{"timestamp":" 947206428833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206430440","data":{"timestamp":" 947206430439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206433390","data":{"timestamp":" 947206433390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206435004","data":{"timestamp":" 947206435003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206437357","data":{"timestamp":" 947206437356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206438952","data":{"timestamp":" 947206438951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206441223","data":{"timestamp":" 947206441223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206442820","data":{"timestamp":" 947206442820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206445056","data":{"timestamp":" 947206445056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206446690","data":{"timestamp":" 947206446689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206448910","data":{"timestamp":" 947206448909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206450938","data":{"timestamp":" 947206450936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206451039","data":{"timestamp":" 947206451039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206464448","data":{"timestamp":" 947206464447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 55d9b1ba-4a79-4d60-95a5-56da26fa28dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206516518","data":{"timestamp":" 947206516518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206521707","data":{"timestamp":" 947206521706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206528538","data":{"timestamp":" 947206528538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206535446","data":{"timestamp":" 947206535446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206540643","data":{"timestamp":" 947206540643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206548710","data":{"timestamp":" 947206548710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206555020","data":{"timestamp":" 947206555020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206561264","data":{"timestamp":" 947206561264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206576286","data":{"timestamp":" 947206576286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206584561","data":{"timestamp":" 947206584561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206594892","data":{"timestamp":" 947206594892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206602697","data":{"timestamp":" 947206602697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206613157","data":{"timestamp":" 947206613157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206622589","data":{"timestamp":" 947206622589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206631960","data":{"timestamp":" 947206631960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206640537","data":{"timestamp":" 947206640537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206648740","data":{"timestamp":" 947206648740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206658130","data":{"timestamp":" 947206658130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206664160","data":{"timestamp":" 947206664160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206672023","data":{"timestamp":" 947206672023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206680245","data":{"timestamp":" 947206680244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206686650","data":{"timestamp":" 947206686649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206698407","data":{"timestamp":" 947206698406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 256aadad-2147-454b-9557-41bff3f43447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206713498","data":{"timestamp":" 947206713498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206719514","data":{"timestamp":" 947206719514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206723808","data":{"timestamp":" 947206723808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206728572","data":{"timestamp":" 947206728572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206733574","data":{"timestamp":" 947206733574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206737715","data":{"timestamp":" 947206737715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206743366","data":{"timestamp":" 947206743366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206748887","data":{"timestamp":" 947206748887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206756038","data":{"timestamp":" 947206756038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206760657","data":{"timestamp":" 947206760656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206766681","data":{"timestamp":" 947206766681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206770857","data":{"timestamp":" 947206770857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206777829","data":{"timestamp":" 947206777829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206783504","data":{"timestamp":" 947206783504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206786726","data":{"timestamp":" 947206786726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206790118","data":{"timestamp":" 947206790118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206793918","data":{"timestamp":" 947206793918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206800702","data":{"timestamp":" 947206800702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206804180","data":{"timestamp":" 947206804180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206811097","data":{"timestamp":" 947206811097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206820431","data":{"timestamp":" 947206820431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206825832","data":{"timestamp":" 947206825832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206829429","data":{"timestamp":" 947206829429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206833554","data":{"timestamp":" 947206833554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206838344","data":{"timestamp":" 947206838344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206844125","data":{"timestamp":" 947206844124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" 47726e93-5614-4a62-a6f7-b9bcc119093e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206881406","data":{"timestamp":" 947206881406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206884890","data":{"timestamp":" 947206884890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206889209","data":{"timestamp":" 947206889209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206893008","data":{"timestamp":" 947206893008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206896450","data":{"timestamp":" 947206896449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206899816","data":{"timestamp":" 947206899815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206903163","data":{"timestamp":" 947206903162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206907414","data":{"timestamp":" 947206907414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206911734","data":{"timestamp":" 947206911734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206918189","data":{"timestamp":" 947206918189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206923658","data":{"timestamp":" 947206923658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206929000","data":{"timestamp":" 947206929000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206935356","data":{"timestamp":" 947206935356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206943569","data":{"timestamp":" 947206943569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206947889","data":{"timestamp":" 947206947889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206951518","data":{"timestamp":" 947206951518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947206958973","data":{"timestamp":" 947206958973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207002641","data":{"timestamp":" 947207002641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207023457","data":{"timestamp":" 947207023457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207031507","data":{"timestamp":" 947207031507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207035486","data":{"timestamp":" 947207035486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207050423","data":{"timestamp":" 947207050423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207066876","data":{"timestamp":" 947207066876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207072558","data":{"timestamp":" 947207072557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207079176","data":{"timestamp":" 947207079176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207102948","data":{"timestamp":" 947207102948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207109586","data":{"timestamp":" 947207109586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947207115365","data":{"timestamp":" 947207115364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_034429"," gameId":" a28a0bca-3dc6-4d37-b210-f2f048db1df9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}